Okay.
We have successfully completed the rebasing process and now we have actually merged all means that were
made and feature on branch into master branch.
And now we can safely delete future one branch.
Let me clear terminal and enter command get branch does redeem feature 1 enter and branch feature 1
was deleted and at the moment we have only a single branch master and no one will step left.
Let's push our changes to a remote repository.
Yet Bush does review and I'm pushing too remote resolving deltas and changes were successfully pushed
a remote repository and file and or get a log amount now you'll see that the local repository and remote
repository are fully synchronized and local master branch and remote master branch point to the same
commit and actually does at last commit made in feature one branch and if I'll go back now to remote
repository here it is and refresh page here you'll see that there are six communes in this repository
and again history is linear near every committee has only a single parent.
That's how rebasing works in action and please use it carefully because again main point is that rebasing
rewrites history it creates brand new means and previous comments made in future branches are actually
lost.
They are garbage collected.
This is all about probation and in the next section we will discuss how to ignore some files that you
don't want to commit.
I'll see you in the next section.
Bye bye.